so let's see if we can do some MSI
protocol transitions let's say we have
two cores with private caches and that
the caches are using MSI to maintain
coherence initially block X is in memory
and no cache has it so here are the
actions of the caches in C1 and c2's
cache core One issues a redex mean while
core2 doesn't do anything what is the
state of block X in C1 cache after this
read is completed and what is the state
of the block X in c2's Cache after this
read on C1 is completed so put your Ms
or I State here and another one here now
let's say that the next axis is that C2
redex after this is completed what is
the new state of X in c1s and c2's cache
and finally C1 does another axis right x
what is now the state in C1 cache after
this right is complete and what's the
state in c2's Cache after this right on
C1 is complete